[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Bull Durham, Crash Davis (played by Kevin Costner) is added to the team to mentor Nuke. What jersey number is Crashs?", "correct_answer": "8", "incorrect_answers": ["3", "18", "13"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Pandas live and travel together.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year did the movie The Trial of Billy Jack come out?", "correct_answer": "1974", "incorrect_answers": ["1975", "1972", "1973"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which former ER star played Chris Gardners wife, Linda in The Pursuit of Happyness?", "correct_answer": "Thandie Newton", "incorrect_answers": ["Thandie Moore", "Julianne Marguiles", "Thandie Marguiles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film industry, this common household item, known as C47, is used as a small gripping tool or a quick fastener, especially when dealing with lighting.", "correct_answer": "A clothespin", "incorrect_answers": ["Foam core", "Tin foil", "Binder clip"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If you needed a good source of iron, this food would be the best.", "correct_answer": "Liver", "incorrect_answers": ["Peas", "Broccoli", "Salt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who came up with the laws of gravity?", "correct_answer": "Newton", "incorrect_answers": ["Pythagoras", "Einstein", "Archimedes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What element is the atmosphere of Jupiter mostly comprised of?", "correct_answer": "Hydrogen", "incorrect_answers": ["Neon", "Helium", "Argon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The movie The Goonies grossed $150,415,432 in 1985?", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was written with fingerprints on the wall behind the upside-down abstract painting in the 1995 thriller movie Seven?", "correct_answer": "Help me", "incorrect_answers": ["Close!", "Greed", "Death"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The element with the symbol Sg is named after an American nuclear chemist and Nobel prize winner, Glenn T. Seaborg.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Spain does not share a border with which one of these countries?", "correct_answer": "Germany", "incorrect_answers": ["Portugal", "France", "Andorra"]}]